Guide to the Ace Reid Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2018-157
  - Framed Items
    - Item 087 "Sir, it ain't exactly our fault. It's them taxes bein' so high a feller hasta steal to pay 'em!" Framed, 17 x 21 (Frame Annex B 6-B-2)
    - Item 088 "Jake, you know that ranch fifty miles west of here you wanted to look at _ _ wul git to lookin' this is it goin' by!" Framed, 17 x 21 (Frame Annex B 6-B-2)
    - Item 089 "Mr. Bookkeeper, I started out forty years ago workin' fer $1 a day, now yore showin' me my profit for the year and I'm still workin' fer $1 a day!" [rancher with no hat] Framed, 17 x 21 (Frame Annex B 6-B-2)
    - Item 090 "Mr. Bookkeeper, I started out forty years ago workin' fer $1 a day, now yore showin' me my profit for the year and I'm still workin' fer $1 a day!" [rancher with hat] Framed, 17 x 21 (Frame Annex B 6-B-2)